James B. Murphy Papers ca.1918-1950 Mss.B.M956
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence, ca.1918-1950 (Box 1-39)
  - Bash, John F
  - Basmaison, L
  - Bass, Allan D
    - Sturm, Ernest
  - Bass, L W
  - Basso, Hamilton
  - Bayet, A
  - Bayne-Jones, S
  - Beard, Edgar
  - Beard, Joseph W
  - Beatti, Manuel
  - Beauchant, R
  - Beeson, Paul B
  - Belgium, Ambassador
  - Belkin, Morris
  - Bell, Gordon Knox
  - Bell, James M
  - Bell, Mabel G
    - World War I
  - Bell, Mrs. Marian
  - Bellinger, Davis & Co.
  - Belmont, Mrs. August
  - Belot, J
    - Association Francaise Pour L'Etude du Cancer
  - Benati, S
  - Benda, Clemens E
  - Benedict, Stanley R
  - Benner, R W
  - Benner, Robert
  - Bentner, R
    - World War I
  - Benton, W B
  - Berge, T O
  - Berger, L
  - Bergey, D H
  - Bergmann, F
  - Berkley, Henry J
  - Berry, George P
  - Berryhill, W R
  - Beth Israel Hospital
  - Betts, Charles T., - Aluminum
  - Bibb, Lewis
    - Simpson, F F
    - Bronson, Margaret
    - Gray, Mrs. A W
    - World War I
  - Bierich, R
  - Bierling, Ben
  - Bigelow, George H
  - Binger, Carl
  - Bigler, L
  - Binkley, Sam
    - McIntire, Ross
  - Binns, E W
  - Biographical Notes
    - Saville, Thorndike
    - Soper, George A
    - Austin, J H
    - Means, J H
  - Biological Abstracts
  - Bird, John
  - Birkhauser, Hans
  - Bittner, J J
  - Black, John T
    - Rhoads, C P
  - Blalock, Alfred
  - Blankenhorn, M A
  - Bloodgood, Joseph C
  - Blumenthal, Ferdinand
  - Blumer, G Alden
  - Blumer, George
  - Board of Visitors of the State Institute for the Study of Malignant Diseases.
    - New York State Health Dept.
    - Godfrey, Edward S., Jr.
    - Lockwood, Paul E
    - Wehr, William H
    - Clapper, Charlotte M
    - Cottis, G W
    - Kress, Louis C
    - Sprickman, Norman C
    - Kirchhofer, A H
    - Dewey, Thomas E
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Levin, Morton L
    - Werner, B J
    - Sells, Charles H
    - Hilleboe, Herman E
  - Boehmig, R
  - Boel, Rene
  - Bohlender, George P
  - Bohuson, Henry F
  - Boisseau, Edna
  - Bond, Earl D
  - Bonnar, James M
  - Bonnelly, Fabio
  - Bordley, James, Jr.
  - Borst, Max
  - Boston Herald, 6 March 1921
  - Bougere, Carl
  - Bourne, Frederick Gilbert
  - Bovie, W T
  - Bowing, H H
  - Bowman, Isaiah
  - Boycott, A E
  - Boyd, John T., Jr.
  - Boyer, Francis
  - Branch, Arnold
  - Branch, Charles F
  - Brandly, C A
  - Branigan, Ruth
  - Bray, Harry A
  - Breakly, James
  - Brecklein, Hugo
  - Bredsdorff, Ingerd
  - Brehmer, William
    - X-Ray
  - Brewer, George
    - Minot, George R
  - Brewer, Joseph
  - Brewster, David Truman, Jr.
  - Breyer, Frank G
  - British Empire Cancer Campaign
    - Johnson, Nelson Tinsley
    - Castle, W R
    - Garton, Richard
    - Chapman, E J C
    - Fry, H J B
    - Cancer Review
    - O'Brien, Daniel P
  - Bronk, Detlev W
  - Bronson, Margaret L
    - Quick, Douglas
    - Churchman, John W
  - Brooks, M M
  - Brooks, Mrs. Mary E
  - Brown, John Crosby
  - Brown, L G
  - Brown, Laurason
  - Brown, Roscoe
  - Brown, Wade
  - Brues, Austin M
  - Bruhlmann, H
  - Brunschwig, Alexander
  - Brush, Edward N
  - Budd, Kenneth P
  - Budd, S W
  - Buffum, William W
  - Burstenbinder, Robert
  - Bulkley, L Duncan
  - Bullen, B C
  - Bunting, C H
  - Burbank, H Russell
  - Burk, Dean
  - Burke, Joseph F
  - Burke's Landed Gentry
  - Burlingame, C C
  - Burmester, Ben R
  - Burnap, Sydney R
    - World War I
  - Burns, Robert W
  - Burrage, Mrs. Martha Merrill Robinson
    - Nield, Marjorie P
  - Burrows, Montrose T
    - Burrows, Harold
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Bustanoby, Mrs. Doris
    - Marvin, Langdon P
    - Parke, John S
  - Butts, Donald C A
  - Byam, W
  - Byrnes, C M
  - Cahill, William M
  - Caisse, Rene M
  - Caldwell, E W
    - Ewing, J
    - Baetjer, F W
    - Imboden
    - Porter, C A
  - Callahan, Maurice
    - Park, David W
    - Brinkley, George E
  - Callahan, W P
  - Callender, George R
  - Calver, George W
    - Richards, A N
    - Major, Randolph T
    - Rhoads, C P
  - Campbell, Edith
    - World War I
  - Campbell, Editha C
  - Canby, Henry S
  - Cannon, Paul R
  - Cancer Congress, Third International, 1939
    - Woglom, William H
    - Wood, Francis Carter
  - Cancer Cures
  - Cancer Cures and Inquiries, 1942
  - Cancer Cures and Inquiries, 1944
  - Cancer Cures and Inquiries, 1945
  - Cancer Cures and Inquiries, 1946
  - Cancer Cures and Inquiries, 1947
  - Cancer Cures and Inquiries, 1948
  - Cancer Cures and Inquiries, 1949
  - Cancer Cures and Inquiries, 1950
  - Cancer Inquiries and Cures
  - Cancer Publications
  - Cancer Research, 1940
    - Schram, Mildred W S
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Woglom
    - Wood, Francis Carter
    - Smith, George M
    - Little, C C
    - Thibaudeau, A A
    - Tannenbaum, Albert
    - Compton, Arthur H
  - Cancer Research, 1941
    - Schram, Mildred W S
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Wood, Francis Carter
    - Bittner, John J
    - Clay, Arthur A
    - Smith, George M
    - Miller, C Phillip
    - Failla, G
    - Karsner, Howard T
    - Doisy, E A
    - Simpson, Burton T
    - Le Compte, Mrs. Jean S
  - Cancer Research, 1942
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Schram, Mildred W S
    - Le Compte, Jean S
    - Woglom, William H
    - Furth, Jacob
    - Kennaway, E L
    - Brunschwig, Alexander
    - Barber, Elizabeth B
    - Queen, Frank B
    - Shear, M J
    - Lucke, Baldwin
    - McCutcheon, Morton
    - Shrigley, E W
    - Rusch, Harold P
  - Cancer Serum Tests Made on 42 Humans.
  - Carnoy, Mme
  - Carr, C McD
    - Grisette, Felix A.
  - Carrel, Alexis
  - Carrington, E S
  - Carter, John Franklin
    - Carter, Lawrence
  - Carter, W S
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Cary, L R
  - Cary, Louis
  - Case, James T
    - Carrel, Alexis
  - Casey, Albert
  - Caspari, Ernst
  - Caspari, W
  - Castelnuovo, Gina
  - Cattell, J McKeen
    - Claude, Albert
    - Minnich, D E
  - Cave, Henry W
  - Cecil, Arthur B
  - Cellard, A Watson
    - World War I
  - Century Club
  - Century Company
    - Howland, Hewitt H
    - Robinson, Henry Martin
    - World's Work
    - Currie, Barton
    - Taylor, Howard Canning
    - Howland, Hewitt H
    - Goebel, Walther F
    - New York Medical Week
    - Ewing, James
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Century Magazine
    - Bloodgood, Joseph C
    - Minot, George R
    - Taylor, Howard Canning
  - Chadbourne, William M
  - Chahovitch, X
  - Chambers, Robert
  - Champlin, George M
  - Chanler, Susan
  - Chapman, E J C
  - Chapple, Bennett
  - Charlton, H R
    - Pitts, Herman C
    - Ewing, James
    - Rowlett, W W
  - Chase National Bank
  - Chatfield, Paul O
  - Chaulmoogra Oil
    - Cranmer, C C
    - Hill, R B
  - Chemists
    - Wyckoff, Ralph W G
    - Browne, A W
    - Burgess, Laurie L
    - Burrows, Montrose T
    - Coolidge, Thomas B
    - Cromwell, H W
    - Cushing, Harvey
    - Gundernatsch, F
    - Roman, Benjamin
    - Brown, Wade
    - Huber, G S
    - Nipps, Mrs. Ruby W
    - Hartline, H K
    - Helmer, Oscar M
    - Linton, R W
    - McGregor, J H
    - Loebel, Robert O
    - McCordock, Howard, A
    - Redfield, Alfred C
    - Rose, W B
    - Shaw, Edwin H., Jr.
    - Stucky, Charles J
  - Cherry, Thomas
  - Chesney, Alan M
    - Rose, Jean E
  - Chidester, F E
    - Page, Irvine H
  - Childs, Charles H
  - Childs, Elizabeth R
  - Childs Memorial Fund see: Jane Coffin Childs Memorial Fund
  - Cholakis, Gus
  - Churchman, John W
    - World War I
  - Clark, Harry
    - Coolidge, W D
    - Whitney, W R
    - Risley, D E
  - Clark, Janet H
  - Clark, Paul F
  - Clark, W Mansfield
  - Clark, Walter, Jr.
  - Clarke, Hans Thatcher
  - Claude, Albert
    - Morton, J J
    - Simpson, Burton K
    - Evans, H M
    - MacLean, Franklin
    - Sly, Maude
    - Burrows, Montrose T
  - Clinical Congress of Surgeons of North America
    - Martin, Franklin H
  - Clippings
  - Clippings - Cancer
    - Ewing, James
  - Clippings - Europe, 1928 July
  - Clippings - Oglethorpe University
  - Cloudman, Arthur M
  - Clowes, G H A
    - Campbell, E D
  - Cluny, Thomas
  - Coar, Herbert G
  - Coates, Mrs. Joseph J
  - Coca, Arthur F
  - Godman, E A
  - Coffey-Humber Treatment
    - Jones, Walter D
    - Brenner, Richard S
    - Knox-Fry, Mrs. Emily Rose
    - Ewing, James
    - Neal, Kemp
    - Bloodgood, Joseph Colt
    - Kilgore, A J
    - Magan, Percy T
    - Coffey, W B
  - Cohn, Alfred E
  - Colby, James H
  - Colby College
    - Lightner, E A
  - Cole, Randall K
  - Cole, Rufus
    - World War I
  - Cole, William H
  - Coler, Bird S
    - Maisin, Joseph
  - Coley, Bradley L
  - Coley, Mrs. Helen
  - Coley, William B
  - Colie, Edward M
  - Collier's National Weekly
  - Collip, J B
  - Combustion Utilities Corporation
  - Committee on Growth of the Division of Medical Sciences, National Research Council.
  - Committee on Maternal Health
    - Dickinson, Robert L
  - Compound "E"
    - Rhoads, Cornelius P
    - Major, Randolph T
    - Calver, George W
    - Weed, Lewis H
    - Kendall, E C
  - Compton, Arthur H
  - Condon, E U
    - Richards, A N
  - Congreso [Tercer] Nacional De Cancerologia Llambes, Juan J
  - Congresses
    - Blakeslee, A F
    - Garvan, Francis P
    - Godart, Justin
  - Connor, C L
  - Conrey, H S
  - Cooksey, Donald
  - Coolidge, W D
    - Flexner, Simon
    - X-Ray
    - Whitney, W R
  - Coombe, Reginald D
  - Cooper, William A
  - Copp, Harry
  - Copp, Owen
  - Corbett, Mrs. Marguerite
  - Corbo Noboa, J M
    - Warren, Andrew J
  - Cornell, W Burgess
  - Cornell University
  - Corscaden, James Albert
  - Cortate Treated - Misc.
  - Coster, Charles Henry
  - Cottenham, Mark, Earl of
  - Coudert, Frederick R., Jr.
  - Coughenour, W C
  - Cowdry, E Vincent
    - Sams, Crawford F
    - Biasi, Margaret
  - Cowperthwaite, I A
  - Craig, Francis N
  - Craig, Stuart L
  - Cramer, Charles
    - Amoss, Harold L
    - Glover, George F
    - Stewart, Harold
    - Arrowsmith, L M
  - Cramer, W
  - Crane, Mrs. Murray
  - Craver, Lloyd F
    - X-Ray
  - Crawford, B L
  - Creedon, Mrs. Julia
    - X-Rays
  - Crile, George
    - Carey, Eben J
    - Rolland, Amy
  - Croninshield, Frank
  - Crowe, Samuel
  - Crowell, Bowman C
  - Crowell, Marion B
  - Cullen, Thomas S
  - Cullis, Winifred C
  - Cumberlege, G F J
  - Cunningham, E Y
  - Curoe, Philip R V
  - Current Researches in Anesthesia and Analgesia
  - Currie, Norman W
    - Koch Cancer Foundation
  - Cushing, Harvey
    - World War I
  - Cutler, Max
  - Cutler, Oran I
  - Cutter, Irving S
  - Dabney, William M
  - Dahlgren, Ulric
  - Dakin, H D
  - Dalldorf, Gilbert
  - Dandy, Walter E
    - Rous, Peyton
  - Daniels, Josephus
  - Darnall, R F
  - Darnell, Carl
  - Davenport, Charles B
  - Davidson, Percy, B
  - Dawson, Alden B
  - Deelman, H T
  - Deering, Thomas G
    - Flexner, Simon
  - De Kruif, Paul
  - Dennis Expedition
    - Sawyer, W
    - Beeuwkes, Henry
  - De Puy, Mrs. Henry F
    - Matthews, Frank S
  - Derby, George
  - De Rivas, Damaso
  - Derow, Harry A
  - De Savitsch, Eugene
  - De Voghel, Mme M A
  - De Vries, W M
    - De Vries, N F
  - Dialysis Apparatus
  - Diefendorf, A R
  - Dingwall, A
  - Diplomate [Magazine]
    - Elwood, Everett S
  - Dobbs, George
  - Dochez, A R
  - Dock, George
  - Dodds, E C
  - Doern, W G
  - Doisy, E A
  - Donaghy, Mrs. Nellie
  - Donkers, A
  - Donner, William H
    - Ewing, James
  - Dorsey, A E
  - Dougherty, T F
  - Douglass, C F
  - Downes, William A
  - Downing, E D
  - Downing, Virginia
  - Draper, George
  - Driessens, J
  - Droogleever Fortuyn, A B
  - Duane, William
  - Duffus, Robert L
  - Duke, W W
  - Duke University
    - Blum, Gilbert
    - Judge, Joseph T
    - Baldwin, Alice M
  - Duke Univ. - Medical School - Applicants
    - Arias, Irwin M
    - Blunt, Barbara
    - Gluksman, Michel A
    - Bernstein, Abraham
    - Swett, Mrs. Elizabeth Alen
    - Gregg, Paul C
    - Gross, Marvin
    - Kanter, Gerald S
    - Lochhead, Archie
    - Treves, Norman
    - Siliciano, Robert V
    - Seton, Paul H
    - Swift, Lucy H
    - Young, Charles G
    - Halter, Howard M
    - Edelman, Jerry
    - Davison, Wilburt C
  - Dulles, John Foster
  - Dunbar, P W
  - Duncan, Rex
  - Dunn, Gano
  - Dunn, Leslie Clarence
  - Duran-Reynals, F
    - Craig, Stuart
    - Berens, Conrad
    - Boyer, Francis
    - Olmstead, Hazel
    - Flinn, Waldo R
  - Du Vigneaud, Vincent
  - Dyer, Helen M
  - Dyott, G M
  - Eagle, Harry
  - East, E M
  - Eberhard, Theodore P
  - Edison, Thomas A
  - Edwards, Mrs. Agnes V
  - Edwards, Dayton J
  - Edwards, J Graham
  - Egan, Mrs. C Wiley
  - Egley, Viola Gray
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Belknap
  - Eisen, Milton J
  - Elasser, Theodore H
    - Olitsky, Peter
  - Eliot, Ellsworth
  - Ellinger, F P
  - Elliott, Mrs. L B
  - Ellis, Robert
  - Elmhurst, Thomas
  - Ely, DeForest
  - Epstein, Alex
  - Erdman, Rhoda
  - Esterbrooks, Dr.
  - Ethyl Urethane Notes
  - Eustes, Mrs.
  - Evans, E Harvey
  - Evans, Lewis M
  - Evans, Sallie
  - Evans, William A
  - Evening Sun, Baltimore
    - Sherwood, Harry S
  - Ewing, James
    - Donner, W H
    - Stewart, Fred
    - Robbins, Harry Pelham
    - Ladd, William S
    - Cole, Rufus I
    - L'Esperance, Elise Strang
    - Rosensteel, Eva G
  - Ewing Fund
    - L'Esperance, E S
  - Ewing, James - Memoir
    - Stewart, Fred
    - Pack, George T
    - Jewett, Frank B
    - L'Esperance, Elise S
    - Martin, Hays
    - Merriman, H Morton
    - Ballantine, Arthur
  - Ewing, William C
  - Failey, Crawford F
    - Lewis, Gilbert N
  - Fairchild, David
    - Russell, Frederick F
  - Farmer, Muriel D
    - Eller, Joseph J
  - Farmer's Federation, Inc.
    - Buckner, Mortimer N
  - Favilli, Giovanni
    - Karsner, Howard T
    - Hawkins, James A
    - Morton, John J
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Bronfenbrenner, Jacques J
    - Banting, F G
    - Simpson, Burton T
    - Cowdry, E Vincent
  - Fearey, Malcolm S
    - Gorham, L W
    - Ordway, Thomas
  - Federal Security Agency
  - Feldman, William H
  - Felton, Floyd D
  - Fensier, M L
  - Ferguson, Mrs. Frances Hand
  - Ferguson, John A
  - Ferrell, Leland R
  - Fialla, G
  - Fibiger, Johannes
  - Fife, Molly
  - Fifth Avenue Hospital, N.Y.C.
    - Kugelmass, I Newton
  - Figarsty, Judith
  - Fike, R H
  - Finsterwald, Louis
  - Fischer, F G
  - Fish, H D
  - Fisher, Albert
  - Flaks, Joseph
    - Russell, Gladys E
    - Gregg, Alan
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Fleming-Hall Tobacco Co., Inc.
  - Flexner, Abraham
  - Flexner, Isadore
  - Flexner, Simon
    - Clark, Harry
    - Jacobs, Philip E
    - Welch, William H
    - Taylor, Kenneth
    - Bull, C G
    - Nakahara, Ward
    - World War I
    - Morgan, Thomas Hunt
    - Austin, J H
    - Fletcher, W M
    - World War I
  - Flinn, Waldo R
    - Russell, Marion D
    - Sommer, Hana
  - Flu, P C
  - Foote, Emerson
  - Forbes, Allan
  - Fortune
    - Davenport, Russell W
    - Murphy, Mary Ellen
    - Solow, Herbert
  - Foss, H L
  - Foster, Robert H
  - Fowler, Thomas
  - Fowler, Virginia N
  - Fraenkel, Manfred
  - Frankel, Lee K
  - Fraps, M
  - Frazier, W L
  - Friedman, Herbert P., Jr.
  - Friedman, Meyer
  - Frissell, Louis
    - Morrison, G H
  - Fromm, Marvin
  - Fulton, Harry C
    - Koch Cancer Foundation
  - Funk, Casimir
    - Claude, Albert
  - Furth, Jacob
  - Futcher, Thomas B
  - Galpin, Perrin C
  - Gardner, Belle F
    - Mathews, Frank S.
  - Gardner, Raymond E
  - Gardner, William U
  - Garland, C M
  - Garland, Gladys
  - Garrison, F H
  - Gas Gangrene Committee
    - World War I
  - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Rhoads, C P
  - Gates, Frederick L
  - Gatty-Kostyal, M
    - TenBroeck, Carl
  - Gavin, Joseph A
    - World War I
  - Gay, Frederick P
  - Gaylord, Harvey R
  - Geiger, J C
  - Genetic Conference
    - Little, C C
  - Gerard, R W
  - Gerdes, Theodore R N
  - Gerhard, Arthur, Jr.
  - German Scientists
    - Bruda, Botho E
    - Lansdown, Frances Shaw
    - Gereb, P
    - Heim, Fr
    - Russell, F F
  - Gersen
    - Nicoll, Matthias
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Gey, George O
  - Gibbons, R A
  - Gilbert, Judson B
  - Gillet, Dr. J. Traitement Du Cancer
  - Ginsburg, Samuel
  - Glenn, John B
  - Glickman, Harry
  - Glover, Eugene C
  - Goddard, Henry M
  - Godfrey, Alfred L
  - Gold, A E
  - Goldenhorn, I Faerber
  - Goldfarb, A J
  - Goldfeder, Anna
  - Golding, John W
  - Goldsmith, E D
  - Goler, G W
  - Goodall, H D
    - Smith, Erwin F
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Goodnow, Frank J
  - Goodpasture, Ernest W
  - Goodson, Louis H
  - Gordon, Myron
  - Gordon, W E
    - Gordon, James P
    - Terry, Arthur H
    - Jennings, Allyn R
  - Gorer, P A
  - Gorham, Grace V
    - Ferguson, J S
    - Pepper, William
  - Gorham, L Whittington
  - Gorog, Nicholas
  - Gosselin, W
  - Gotham, Hospital, N.Y.C.
    - Conner, Lewis A
  - Gowen, John W
  - Grabowski, John D
  - Gradwohl, R B H
    - Noguchi, Hideyo
  - Graef, F W, Jr.
  - Graf, Lise Lotte
  - Graham, Frank P
    - Berryhill, W Reece
  - Graham Department Stores Co.
  - Grant, Daniel L
  - Grant, Wilson C
  - Granville-Walker, Mrs.
    - Rhoads, C P
  - Granwick, Ann
  - Grattan, James F
  - Gratwick, William H
  - Graves, James C, Jr.
  - Graves, Ralph H
  - Graves, Stuart
    - Ewing, James
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Gray, Mrs. A W
  - Greb, Raymond J
  - Greene, Harry S N
  - Greene, M V
  - Greene, Roger S
  - Greenough, Robert B
    - Ewing, James
  - Gregg, Alan
  - Gregoire, Charles
  - Greville, G D
  - Groover, Thomas A
  - Gross, Ludwik
    - Mirsky, I Arthur
  - Gruenwald, Rudolf
  - Guareschi, Celso
  - Guion, Connie M
  - Gumbel, Robert W
    - Daly, W T
  - Gunn, C K
  - Guy, W Bryant
  - Guzman, Leonardo
  - Gwyn, Norman B
  - Gye, W E
  - Haam, Emerich von
  - Hackett, L W
    - X-Ray
  - Haddow, Alexander
  - Hadley, F B
  - Haggart, William W
  - Hahn, Julius
  - Hale, F M
  - Halsted, W S
    - Davidson, Rolland A
    - Hill, Mrs. Else H
  - Hamburger, Louis P
  - Hamill, Samuel McClintock
  - Hamilton, James B
  - Hammett, Frederick S
  - Hance, Robert T
    - Sieg, L P
    - Collins, H H
  - Hand, Mrs. Frances
  - Harmon, Lena M
  - Harris, Donald
  - Harrison, Edwin M
  - Harrison, Ursula C
    - Lewis, R H
  - Harsem, Otto
  - Harvard Club
    - Logan, Sheridan A
    - Reid, Howard
  - Harvey, George
  - Harvey Society
    - Edwards, Dayton J
    - Cattell, McKeen
    - West, Randolph
    - Cohn, A E
    - Emerson, Haven
    - Bradley, Joseph A
    - Ohrenberger, Henry W
    - McLaughlin, James A
    - Schirmer, Adelbert F
  - Hastings, Baird
  - Hatfield, Nathan Lewis, Lecture
    - Pemberton, Ralph
    - Miller, T Grier
    - Stroud, William D
    - Austin, J Harold
    - Reimann, Stanley P
  - Havana University
    - U.S. Dept. of State
    - Dochez, Alphonse R
    - White, Philip R
  - Hawkins, James A
    - Brown, E W
  - Hazlehurst, George
    - Berry, George P
  - Healey, John
  - Healy, M
  - Heaney, Norman S
  - Heat Curve
  - Heath, Harold
  - Heddinger, Mabel L
  - Hegner, C F
  - Heidelberger, Michael
  - Heilman, Fordyce
  - Heim, Fr
  - Heiser, Victor George
  - Hektoen, Ludvig
  - Helmer, Oscar M
    - Rous, Peyton
    - Clowes, G H A
  - Henderson, Archibald
  - Hensey, Joseph C
  - Herald Tribune
    - Grant, Lester
  - Herbert, Albert E
  - Hersey, Harold W
    - Hussey, R G
  - Hess, Alfred F
  - Heston, W E
  - Heyman, Albert
  - Hibbs, Russell A
  - Higgins, George M
  - Hilcken, John Allen
  - Hill, Elsa
  - Hill, Frank E
  - Hill, Mrs. Frank E
    - World War I
  - Hill, Ruth
  - Himwich, Harold E
  - Hinkle, Margaret
    - Seuber, Mrs. H L
    - Eliot, Elsworth
  - Hochstetler, Mrs. J M
  - Hodges, J Allison
  - Hodges, Paul C
    - Pearce, Richard M
    - X-Ray
  - Hodo, Niculae
  - Hoechstetter, S
  - Hoenigsberger, Emmy
  - Hofbauer, Isfred
  - Hoffman, Donald C
  - Hoffman, Joseph G
  - Hoffman, William W
  - Hogeboom, George H
    - Hogeboom, Mrs. Corneil
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Jacocks, W P
  - Holden, Earl C
  - Holder, Amy
    - Hartwell, John A
  - Hollander, Franklin
  - Holmes, George
  - Holt, Benton B
  - Holt, L Emmett, Jr.
  - Home for Incurables
  - Homer, Francis T
  - Hooker, Charles W
  - Horning, Eric
  - Hoskins, Roy G
  - Hotchkiss, Henry G
  - Houghson, Walter
  - Howard, John J
  - Howard, Mrs. Sidney
  - Howe, F Stanley
  - Howell, William H
  - Hoxsey Treatment of Cancer
    - Spencer, R R
    - Rhoads, C P
  - Hubbard, Joshua C
    - X-Ray
    - Codman, E A
  - Hubel, Mrs. Joseph
  - Huecker, John
  - Hufty, Page
    - X-Ray
  - Huggins, Charles
  - Hume, May
  - Hurd, Eleanor
  - Hurd, Henry M
  - Huseby, Robert
  - Hussey, Raymond
  - Hyde, Roscoe B
  - Hyman, Harold Thomas
  - Inbred Chickens
    - Olson, Carl, Jr.
    - Van Roekel, Henry
    - Little, C C
  - Ince, Kathleen
  - Ingersoll, E S
  - Ingersoll, Ralph McA
    - Fortune (Magazine)
  - Institute for Research
    - Prescott, John A
  - Institute for Research in Biography.
  - Institute of International Education
    - Fisher, Edgar J
  - Instituto Medico Curie
  - International Association of Microbiologists St. John-Brooks, R
    - Sawyer, W A
    - Dawson, M H
  - International Cancer Research Foundation
  - International Congress of Medicine
  - Invitations
  - Irish Cancer Research Institute
    - Pearce, Richard M
    - Cassidy, Louis
  - Irwin, D
  - Iselin, Ernest
  - Iselin, Louis
  - Iselin, O'Donnell
  - Itami, Shigemitsu
  - Ivy, A C
    - Smith, George M
    - Spencer, R R
  - Jaches, L
  - Jackson, Chevalier
  - Jackson, Ethel R
    - World War I
  - Jackson, Henry, Jr.
  - Jackson, Roscoe B., Memorial Laboratory
    - Snell, George D
    - Bittner, John J
    - Little, C C
    - Cloudman, A M
    - Hamlin, G O
    - Murray, William S
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Scott, J P
    - Gantt, Robert A
    - Hummel, Katharine P
    - Fielder, Judith H
    - Slocum, Rosalie
  - Jackson, Roscoe B., Memorial Laboratory - Reorganization
    - Snell, George D
    - Hamlin, George O
    - Jackson, Richard W
    - Runner, Meredith
    - Ripley, James H
    - Little, C C
  - Jacobi, Oliver
  - Jacobs, John L
    - Sommers, Sheldon
  - Jacobs, Thornwell
  - Jacocks, W P
  - Jacquez, John A
  - Jaleski, Thomas C
  - James, Henry
  - James, Walter B
  - Jane Coffin Childs Memorial Fund for Medical Research
    - Childs Memorial Fund
    - Meader, R G
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Claude, Albert
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Holbrook, Mildred P
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Thompson, Helen P
    - Winternitz, M C
  - Jares, John J, Jr.
  - Jeck, Howard S., Jr.
  - Jennings, Percy H
    - Eddy, Walter H
  - Jewett, Frank B
    - Bowman, Isaiah
  - Jobling, James W
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital. Name: Juan Dice
  - Johns Hopkins University
    - Roulston, R B
    - Edmunds, C K
    - Baker, Lawrence H
    - Weed, Lewis H
    - Acton, C B
    - Thomas, Henry M., Jr.
    - Burgan, Harry C
    - Chatfield, Paul
    - Longcope, W T
    - Chesney, Alan M
    - Baetjer, Walter A
    - Clark, W Mansfield
  - Johnson, Catherine
  - Johnston, Kathleen
  - Jones
  - Jones, Daniel Fiske
  - Jones, Frederick S
  - Jones, Herman D
  - Jones, Thomas
    - Foss, H L
  - Jones, Thomas H
    - Prest, John B
  - Journal of Cellular and Comparative
    - Physiology
    - Harvey, E Newton
  - Journal of Clinical Investigation
    - Austin, J Harold
  - Journal of General Physiology
    - Osterhout, W J V
  - Journal of Immunology
    - Coca, Arthur F
  - Journal of the American Medical Association
  - Judkins, Esther
  - Julianelle, L A
  - Kamerling, Samuel E
  - Kaminskas, Joseph T
  - Karnofsky, David A
  - Karsner, Howard T
  - Kaye, Robert
  - Kearny, Mrs. Elizabeth
    - Halsted, W S
  - Keller, Florence
    - Haden, Russell L
  - Kellersberger, E R
  - Kellogg, Gertrude
    - Howe, George
  - Kelly, M F
  - Kendall, Arthur I
    - World War I
  - Kendall, E C
  - Kennaway, Ernest L
    - Schramm, Mildred
  - Kent, Mrs. Rosemary M
  - Keyes, Joseph
  - Kickton, Dr.
  - Kibler, W H
  - Kidd, John G
  - Kiernan, Thomas
  - Kilgore, J R
  - Kimball, John A C